Look at this! The likes are through the roof!
Thailand, Indonesia, even America!
Folks from all over the world are liking our videos!
Great job, Hana-chan.
You and Eun Ho did all the hard work.
Don't say that.
- Did you have breakfast?
- Nope.
Shall we grab something from the store?
- Okay.
- Let's go.
I'm starving!
♫♫
[People are really liking it, huh?]
[Episode 3: Full Bloom]
Oh? When did you get these?
I've got everything.
Apply it for me! I even lowered myself to your height.
Did you see the posts from Hana's team?
It's insane, right?
I really thought I was eating pork cutlets with Gu Eun Ho.
It isn't just eating with him!
His precious hands cut it for me!
It'll be amazing if it became a series.
Oh, a series is a great idea.
But I guess someone's going to be jealous if they blow up.
Come on.
Let's go, let's go.
A series?
Ji Ah!
- Did I scare you?
- Yeah, what else?
Especially after you filmed all that.
Sorry, I was too excited.
Actually, I hate it when people touch me.
Really? I didn't know, I'm so sorry.
I'll be careful from now on.
Sorry, you had to put up with me for so long.
Ji Ah, do you want something sweet?
A candy or some gummies?
Are you going to make a series?
The stuff about male friends.
You saw it?
I was about to go to bed,
but the notifications kept popping up.
At first, I thought I was dreaming.
Even now, it still feels unreal.
So, is it going to be a series?
Yes.
I owe it all to you.
You said that even a selfie would work.
Instead of selfies, I uploaded memories.
I work my life out trying to complete assignments,
but you sound like you're just making memories with the guys.
Ji Ah, you're capable.
I have nothing.
Eun Ho and Si Woo are doing all the hard work.
I guess that's right.
Group distribution is all about luck.
♫♫
I'm going to throw up my lunch.
Hey, get up. We have to practice.
We can't get up, or it'll be disastrous.
Just curious, but do you have insurance?
No clue...
Should I call my mom?
What? Go on sleeping.
- Should I turn off the lights?
- Ji Ah.
Give us a break. Ba Reun, tell her.
Let her know how hard we were practicing!
You're so mean!
The like button is the issue.
Why can we only like a post once?
Why? Why's that?
Spare a thought for people who want to watch it 100 times.
You're really something.
I can watch this 200 times.
I'm really sorry, Eun Ho.
Get her here. Right now.
Hello.
I still haven't gotten their selfie.
You're really cunning.
I heard from Eun Ho.
Whatever that happened...
Let's leave it in the past.
I have a different task for you today.
You know that my dream is to be Eun Ho's girlfriend, right?
But...
Your group's reels are a real feast!
It's freaking crazy, like I'm on a date with Eun Ho.
Is that a compliment?
Hell yes!
You have our approval!
Our approval!
So, I've gathered some fan requests.
Hear me out.
The amusement park, arcade, karaoke, cafe, one-day classes...
- Han River.
- That's a great idea.
Seongsu-dong, Sangsu-dong. These are different places.
Even a beauty shop trip will be great! A makeover!
I'll think about it.
But what's that about Eun Ho and the selfie?
Oh, I know that you screwed things up.
Too obvious. He came after me less than 10 minutes after.
Exactly.
Please do a Han River video! How about a picnic?
- That'll be amazing!
- Packing lunch boxes too!
Please! Make sure it happens!
- Thanks.
- Please!
Where were you? We waited for ages.
Waited? You're clearly having fun.
You should've said something before leaving.
I'm their manager.
I can't fall for him!
I have to get used to this!
[April Week 1 Acting Course Workshop:
Social Media Posts Results]
- Hello!
- Hana, come over! You did well!
I thought the assignment was too hard
since you hadn't posted anything even until yesterday.
How did you climb to the top in just one day?
I guess you really thought this over.
Every Friday, I'll put up the results.
I'll look forward to your works.
Thank you very much.
[Follower: Hana, Ji Ah, Seul Gi, Bit Na]
[Likes: Hana, Ji Ah, Seul Gi, Bit Na]
Wow, I'm last.
Ji Ah's going to be first anyway... what the heck?
- She isn't!
- Dang!
Was she overtaken in just 10 hours?
Oh dear, Ji Ah.
This is the first time you've come in second, right?
Shouldn't this call for a commemorative photo?
I'll be first again, so shut up and get lost.
Ji Ah.
Huh? She told me to get lost, but she left.
Her temper's crap.
Her personality's out of this world, huh.
Hana-chan.
She never cared to make friends before.
But she lets you get close because you're Ba Reun's cousin.
So, here's the thing.
If you don't have anyone to hang out with, join us.
Aren't you going to continue with the series?
Take turns reading it out.
Are we really doing this?
I saw it 1,219 times! Heart!
My life has been blessed. Wish you all the best.
My drowsiness is all gone now! Thank you!
Let's vote. Affection or aloof?
My pain's all gone now!
Si Woo, I love you so much!
My blood type? You, my ideal type.
I heard that roses are in season now.
Si Woo's rosy cheeks.
You don't rinse after brushing, right?
Because you're already my prince!
Eun Hoo's eyes are brighter than my future!
I want to be the owner of this phone!
The rest are in English, so I don't understand.
Don't you think anything about these?
They're really interesting.
Hana-chan did nothing except film them!
But I'm the only one serious about this!
You should just film us casually, too. Don't be too serious.
Are you telling me to copy her?
Why fight so desperately for first place?
Look at me, I'm living so well ranking 20th in the Acting course.
Guys like you make me hate group projects.
"Guys like you"? What the heck?
Why are you dating her?
Don't say that.
It'll be nice... to be first.
I'll repeat exactly as Ji Ah said.
Okay.
She's very sensitive and concerned about her grades.
During the workshop, keeping your distance
as competitors is better.
Is Ji Ah...
being nice to me just because I'm your cousin?
Be honest.
That was how it started,
but she seemed to gradually treat you as her friend.
Right now, I think she's riled up
because grades matter to her.
Tell her...
I've always seen her as a friend.
I'll also continue to be her friend.
Got it. I'm on your side this time.
Don't be too upset.
Leave it to me.
Hi.
Good morning.
Did you think about what we told you?
How are things going?
- Good.
- Promise to make them pack lunches.
Do you know what Polaroids are?
Taking photos with this will be even more awesome.
Hey. Are you even listening to me?
Damn, is Gu Eun Ho insane? My dear kitty...
Yikes.
Long time no see, "Ugh" Ji Ah. You make my eyes hurt.
Hang on.
What?
I guess you aren't keeping up with old habits.
Of course not, the manager's doing everything for me.
So dumb.
It isn't for you, they're enjoying their time.
Who are you talking about?
Gu Eun Ho and his manager.
They're recording their memories.
Social media has always been an exhibit of happiness.
I've heard that she visits his house often.
Is that why he came to me?
Is that why he calls her that?
Damn it.
If you don't show any respect,
I'll do the same.
Eun Ho?
This looks like someone...
Did you fall out with Shin Ji Ah?
No.
It isn't a fight, we're just giving each other space.
What? Are you two a couple?
What's the most important thing to you?
What about you?
Friends.
Try guessing where it is.
If you get it right, you'll make up with Ji Ah.
I told you, we didn't fight.
The right hand.
You're right.
Take it.
Isn't this...
I have more at home.
Thank you.
I'll keep it with me like a lucky charm.
A lucky charm that gives me courage.
Do whatever you want.
I'm off.
What is it this time?
Now that I think about it,
your face doesn't appear in the reels.
I guess I can film Eun Ho, too.
You can't do that. It's our course's assignment.
I'm also great at video editing.
Let's crush Shin Ji Ah for good this time.
Don't wanna do it?
You're using your assignment as an excuse
to make happy memories with our Eun Ho.
What have you been doing in the club room?
Did you come here to seduce Eun Ho?
If you become a manager, your artistes' lives will be ruined.
A manager who's so satisfied with her job
and brimming with ulterior motives.
A scheming and utterly disgusting manager.
Go bother Cheon Si Woo.
Why are you clinging to Eun Ho...
Stop messing with me!
It's your turn next.
You trampled over what I treasure the most.
What? The keychain?
What's the big deal with that?
This isn't the first time you're doing this.
At first, you wanted to send Ji Ah to hell.
Have you been to hell yourself?
I have.
Secondly, Si Woo.
Are you even worthy of saying his name?
Thirdly, Eun Ho.
Dream about becoming a human
before thinking about being his girlfriend.
Lastly, Suzu and me.
I'll count to five.
Get out of my sight.
One, two, three...
What happened?
She's definitely a gangster's daughter.
What?
There's something really off about her.
Interesting.
I can't sit with her.
I'm also really scared of her now.
She's like a different person.
But at least she didn't use her fists.
So handsome!
So freaking good-looking!
And he's so tall! I bet he's a model!
Take a photo! Quick!
But can we just take photos?
Here, wear this.
I think people recognize you.
Let's go. Si Woo says he'll be late.
But people are staring.
Fine, give it to me.
The weather's great today.
What should we do?
Let's start with eating instant noodles,
and then riding the duck boats.
Do you get motion sickness?
Let's have a picnic or something.
A picnic?
You should've said so earlier.
I would've prepared for it.
There's nothing much to prepare.
What are you doing?
- Follow me.
- Hey!
What is all this?
What do you think? I tried to fit our group's concept.
We had a concept?
You came up with it, eating and having fun without worries.
Come on, sit down.
I bet you're hungry.
Hana-chan, let's watch a movie.
I picked these movies.
Want to watch them?
I like this one.
How about watching this?
Or this one?
A kind male friend who prepared a surprise picnic.
Skip the movie. Let's play games.
The loser gets flicked on the forehead.
Aren't you going to take a block?
Are you just going to film?
Hey.
Hana-chan, it's your turn.
♫♫
An aloof male friend who flicked my forehead gently.
Hang on!
♫♫
And me, smiling brightly without any worries.
Make way. I'll do it.
It's almost done anyway.
I guess you're having fun.
Yeah!
But...
you're a manager, so why are you acting?
[Epilogue]
Sorry.
Sorry, Suzu.